KAORI ERA

Web Developer

+1 236-878-1394 | kestudyforemail@gmail.com | https://www.kestudies.com

PROFILE:

A front-end developer who has a hardware background of 9+ years and loves building creative web applications that make life easier. A hard worker who has the experience to make products as both an engineer and a PL. SKILLS: HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, React, Node.js, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Firebase, Heroku, Git/Github, Bitbucket, Mongoose, Gimp, C and hardware skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

FreeLiveNet Technology Corp

Junior Web Developer | 01 June, 2022 - Present

• Implement maintenance on a prototype website created with several hardware devices.

Microcontroller Programmer | 01 April, 2022 - 31 May, 2022

 Make a prototype using some hardware device(ESP8266, Arduino) and draw the electrical circuit of it.

Coeus Technologies

Web Developer | 25 October, 2021 - 31 January, 2022

- Making a website with HTML, CSS, Animation(Haiku), and PHP.
- Managed user flows and wireframes.

NOEX inc.

Hardware Engineer, Embedded Software Engineer, Procurement, Design for manual | October, 2017 - July, 2021

- Develop products (e.g, Nurse call, Light Alarm Clock, Watching system for children, and so on) from circuit design to component consolidation, mounting, evaluation, and factory assembly instructions.
- Managed part-time workers.

NIDEC COPAL CORPORATION

Embedded Software Engineer | August, 2016 - October, 2017

- Develop Android Application for Actuator demo.
- Development of microcontroller program to control Actuator from Android smartphone.
- Assistance with technical questions to salesperson abroad. (Attending CES 2017 as well)

BUFFALO INC.

Hardware Engineer, Embedded Software Engineer | April, 2012 - August, 2016

- Develop some products both scratching and improving as a hardware engineer, an embedded software engineer, and a project leader.
- Responsible for circuit design, circuit board production, drawing inspection, evaluation, parts examination, and negotiation with related departments (manuals, standards, other development departments, etc).
- Responsible for cost reduction design of products.

EDUCATION:

September, 2021 - August, 2022 | Cornerstone International Community College Of Canada

Diploma of Web And Mobile App Development - Vancouver, Canada

- Acquired front-end skills such as HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, React, React Hooks, Redux, Next.js, and TypeScript
- Acquired back-end skills such as Java, Node.js, Express, Python, MySQL, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB

April, 2008 - March, 2012 | Nagasaki Institute of Applied Science

Bachelor's degree of Engineering - Nagasaki, Japan